> > Brian Holt: 我想说的关于包裹的第一件事是我教过，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So the first thing I wanna
say about Parcel is that I have taught,
在这类的历史上，我教了 Webpack 和 Webpack 是一个非常棒的工具。
historically in this class, I have taught
Webpack and Webpack is a phenomenal tool.
它也是 OpenJS 基金会的一部分。
It is part of
the OpenJS Foundation as well.
Fronend Masters 有个不错的课程
There is a great course in
Frontend Masters about it.
如果你想学习 Webpack 和 React ，我就用 React V3 教它。
If you wanna learn Webpack and
React together I teach it with React V3.
如果你想看看那还真是太有效了
And that's still totally valid
if you wanna check that out.
但我今天要用另一个包裹
But I'm gonna use a different
packager today that is called Parcel.
我选择跟派塞尔一起教的原因是它非常的手断。
The reason why I chose to teach with
Parcel is it's extremely hands-off.
你只要把它指向一个文件
You just point it at a file and
它只是把它自己的一切都做出来了
it just kind of figures it
everything out by itself.
它没有配置。
There's no configuration to it.
Webpack 是惊人的。
Webpack is phenomenal.
它超级强大。
It's super powerful.
如果你有你需要做的事
If you have crazy things
you need to do with it,
Webpack 是你的朋友在做这些疯狂的事情。
Webpack is your friend in
doing crazy stuff like that.
但要建立起来有点困难
But it's kinda difficult to set up.
权力很复杂是必然的，对吧 ?
It's inevitable that with
power comes complexity, right?
所以说我喜欢这两种工具
So suffice to say I love both tools.
我只是选择今天的包裹我们就能集中精力
I'm just choosing Parcel today so
that we can focus on React and
不一定集中在捆束器上
not necessarily focus on the bundler.
我们现在要做的是我们会说晚上晚上会装 D 包的
What we're gonna do now is we're gonna say
npm install D parcel- bundler like that.
那只需要第二个 cuz 就有很多东西了
That one takes a second cuz there's
a lot of stuff that comes with it.
>> Brian Holt: 这是将每个代码捆绑在一起的实际工具，并且
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This is the actual tool
that will bundle every code together, and
准备好了
get it ready.
1 表示开发环境， 2 表示生产环境。
1 for your development environment,
and 2 for production.
而且真的很聪明
And it's really smart.
你把它指向你的索引 html 文件
You just point it at
your index html file and
它通过找出所有路径来发现所有路径
it discovers all the paths just
by figuring everything out.
它就像这是一个 TypeScript 文件，或者是一个 JavaScript
And it figures out like this is
a TypeScript file, or this is a JavaScript
文件，或者这是一个 CSS 文件，它对您的所有内容都是灵活的。
file, or this is a CSS file and it just
neatly packages everything for you.
这是一个令人印象深刻的工具。
It's a pretty impressive tool.
>> Brian Holt: 我实际上经常使用它。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It's one I
actually I use quite frequently.
背包和包裹都值得支持
And both Webpack and
Parcel definitely worth supporting.
他们都有开放的收藏者，所以你会有自己的倾向。
They both have open collectors, so
that's something you feel inclined to do.
你可以看到他们在那里为你删除了一个链接。
You can see that they actually
drop a link in there for you.
>> Brian Holt: Frontend Masters ，感谢 Frontend Masters。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Frontend Masters does,
thanks Frontend Masters.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，既然我们已经这样做了，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
now that we've done that,
我要你去你的包里
I want you to go into your package.json.
我们将在这里添加另一个将是 dev的脚本。
And we're going to add another script
in here that's going to be dev.
>> Brian Holt: 这将显示包裹 src/index.html。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
this is gonna say parcel src/index.html.
所以你和 Parcel 要做的就是把它点在 index.html 上
So again, all you have to do with Parcel
is you just point it at the index.html
把所有东西都给你
file and
it just figures everything else for you.
>> Brian Holt: 现在我可以进入我的收养了。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
now I can go into my adopt me.
首先我想说的是
Well, so first thing I wanna mention here.
这让我很困惑，直到有人把它指向我。
This was confusing to me for a long
time until someone pointed it out to me.
就像我一样，它怎么知道包裹是什么，对吧 ?
As I was like,
how does it know what parcel is, right?
我觉得这里没有包裹是吧
I don't think I have parcel
available here, right,
它说找不到包裹指令
it says parcel command not found.
就像它是怎么知道的
So like how does it know that?
如果您在此处的节点模块中使用，即所有节点所在的位置，
Well if you go inside of your node modules
here, which is where all of your node,
当我说 npm 安装捆绑软件时，它就会进入节点模块。
when I say npm install bundle there,
that's where it goes into node modules.
还有一个秘书目录她
And there is a secret.bin directory her.
我能用的各种不同的二进制工具
Of all the various different
binary tools I can use, right?
其中一个在这里叫做包裹，它连接到包裹式的捆绑器。
And one of them in here is called parcel,
which is connected to parcel-bundler.
所以它就是这样找到的
So that's how it finds it.
>> Brian Holt: Echo 不在这里，例如， Echo只是像麦克一样的一部分。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Echo's not in here right,
for example, Echo's just part of like Mac.
但它能在这里找到包裹和漂亮的
But it is able to find parcel and
prettier in here.
所以，就这样，你就知道了，这就是如何连接在一起的。
So, just so you know that that's
how that gets connected together.
>> Brian Holt: 现在我可以说， npm 运行 dev。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
now I can say, npm run dev.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍特( Brian Holt ) : 它会把所有东西都放在一起。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
it's gonna build all the stuff together.
它在 1.76 秒后就已经准备好了。
And it's ready in 1.76 seconds.
你可以看到这里有一个 dist 和一个 .cache 的导演。
You can see here that there's now
a dist and a .cache director.
这是 Parcel 为你创造的
That is something that Parcel creates for
you.
你可以基本上忽略它，现在我可以打开了。
You can just basically ignore it,
and I can open now.
所以如果我 Cmd + click 此，它将在我的浏览器中打开。
So if I Cmd + click this,
it'll open in my browser.
你可以看到，神奇的是，我正在使用 localhost:1234 ，但是
And you can see, magically,
I'm running on localhost:1234, but
现在包裹被包裹包裹
now this is being packaged by Parcel.
> > Brian Holt: 现在有一些很酷的东西。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now there's some
pretty cool stuff about this.
如果我进入 app.js 和
If I go into app.js and
我改变了这个， > > Brian Holt: 我不知道，
I change this to be,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I don't know,
在这里再加上一个 " 收养我 " 我就省了这个
maybe add another Adopt Me in here,
and I save this.
它会自动刷新我的页面。
It automatically refreshes my page for
you.
因此，它会为您提供免费的热模型刷新。
So it does a hot model refresh for
you out of the box for free.
你不用做任何事都是有用的
You don't have to do anything about it,
it just works.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And that's really it,
我们不会再配置包裹了
we're not gonna configure
parcel anymore than that.
它很聪明就能找到其他的东西
It's smart enough to figure
everything else out.